Hurry, take them away.
So since that time,
He had no intention of leaving me alive.
I knew that Xiao Lan
You will never hurt me.
She's like my sister.
How could you poison me?
that way,
My mother died that year
It certainly wasn't that simple.
It's Xue Shi Yan.
All of this was done by Xue Shi Yan.
Having such an evil father,
You are really unlucky.
in my heart,
He's not my father anymore.
Since he wants to take advantage of me,
I will let him use me as he wants.
I must help them
To achieve justice for them.
I have already sent Cui Hu
To investigate the source of the fabric.
Don't act rashly right now.
Protecting yourself is most important.
Who is depicted in this painting?
This painting was painted by you, General.
It's Xue Keying.
Did I draw it?
After I burned that Qu Qingyun painting,
You painted another one yourself,
I happily stuck it in the middle.
The face of Shiye Ke Ying
Not that big.
No, I have to adjust it.
General, do you want to go to the secret room?
Secret room.
These paintings and secret messages,
They are all evidence in the case of collusion with the enemy.
General, don't you remember?
You have investigated all this yourself.
It is evidence related to the issue of collusion with the enemy
Which happened five years ago.
Yes.
Since I was injured,
I don't remember a lot of things anymore.
What do you think that
Help me remember?
The general's father, Marquis Zhongjing
And Duke Ying
They were the right and left arms of the late Emperor
They both come from a military background
The old Marquis took over
Xue Shi Yan's Command Seal
After that, he won many battles
For this reason, he was appreciated by the late emperor
General
I doubted it at the time
It was Xue Shi Yan who leaked the military information
So all these years
I was investigating this matter
Although we got caught
Many northern border spies
But none of them were
He was ready to confess to Xue Shi Yan
All we know is
They are when communicating
They use this deer totem
As a secret code
So, Ning
My marriage to the Xue family
It is in order to find evidence
And revenge for my family
therefore
I don't know
Whether we have exchanged
Our souls, really
Ning Yuan Zi
when
Will you wake up?
Ning Yuan Zi
If you don't wake up
Your position as a leader
It will become mine
Brother Ning
If you don't wake up
I will be angry with you
Ning Yuan Zi
I found evidence of Xue Shi Yan betraying the enemy
I found it
Ning Yuan Zi
Why is there no reaction again?
I did not expect
That you carry on your shoulders
Deep, bloody revenge
All day look
As if you don't care about anyone
While you hide all these things in your heart
Rest assured
If you don't really wake up
I am, Xia Yi Mo
I will do the role for you perfectly
I will help you until the end
Don't move
Sister Wan
Mr. Chu
I went outside the ducal palace
I wandered there for two days
And I didn't see
Miss Ke Ying
Is she okay lately?
Is she sad?
Because of your marriage to General Ning?
For this reason?
This is good
Miss Ke Ying is a character
Strong and able to move forward
sometimes
Person's appearance
It does not reflect his reality
I hope, Sister Wan
Don't misunderstand it
The feelings are real
They often appear
Through experiments
Yes
She was helping me all the time
While I blamed her for acting on her own
My fate and your fate now
are linked to each other
If you die
I won't live either
You disobedient and traitorous daughter
You really rebelled
Ning Yuan Zi
He was not sincere in proposing to your sister
He was taken from your sister
A hostage to control you
To achieve the goal of control
On the Duke's Palace
In my eyes
Miss Ke Ying
She is the best girl in the world
and the most beautiful
She always doesn't hesitate
In thinking about others
She's just a stupid girl
She thinks she has nine lives
my daughter
Where were you?
If anything bad happens to you
How will I live after you?
Is there no news about Ke Ying yet?
my lord.
We searched the entire city,
But we found no trace of Second Miss.
But we saw Zhou Qingyun,
Ning Yuanzi had released her.
Ning Yuanzi this,
What on earth does he want to do?
Spread the word.
The way information is transmitted has changed.
Don't act rashly.
Yes.
We have orders from the general.
To enter and exit the General's Palace,
The personal identification plate must be presented.
Being a general is really tiring.
I will sleep.
My mom!
Who is your mother?
He hurried over and handed my daughter Ying'er to me.
Let's go!
Go.
faster.
Ying Er!
What did you do to my beautiful daughter?
Nice and pure?
What did you do with it?
This is your praise
It makes me feel ashamed.
I didn't do anything.
I put it here
For her safety.
I'll take it with me.
Aren't you afraid?
I am by one order
Can I make you and your daughter disappear?
You can kill me
But Ying Er
She has real feelings for you
No, no, no
no
Since you are
You fear for your daughter to die to this extent
Then you have to answer my questions
genuinely
Good
I will say
I will tell everything
Has Duke Ying recently...
With anything
suspicious?
Did he take any paintings with him when he left?
Or met anyone?
It was recently
Sometimes he comes out with paintings
Saying that he will exchange technical experiences with his colleagues
But he did not do so in recent days
So where were they meeting?
Do you remember?
When he comes out
No one is allowed to accompany him
I am just a woman from his household
How can I intervene?
but
Looks like it's tomorrow
He will go out to meet his friends
That's all I know
I told you everything
Now, can you excuse me?
By taking Ying Er?
You can't take it
You
But you can stay here
To treat it
But
Xue Keying will stay in my palace
And the questions I just asked you
If you dare leak a word of it
I will not divulge a single word
Tsoi ho
What's up?
What do you want from me?
I remembered.
In the British Duke's Palace
Similar panels also exist.
They are painted on the same type of canvas.
How did you forget that?
He still has a lot of paintings in his storage.
There must be evidence of it.
I'll make Tsui Ho steal it.
How did you know?
Those paintings in my palace storeroom?
Usually wealthy families
Her treasures are in store.
But I saw those paintings,
They look like ordinary paintings.
There are no deer-shaped totems on it.
If those panels are used
To transfer information,
That information
It must be on the totems.
So if there are no totems,
Does this mean we can't use it?
To condemn him?
decent.
Tomorrow I will make Tsui Ho
watching him,
To see what secret characters he meets,
We will try to catch him red-handed.
Many thanks to the Duke for his generous donation
To help us rebuild the academy.
I would like to offer a toast to the Duke
Take this silver and use it first
If it is not enough
So send someone next month
To take more of my palace
Thanks for your interest, Duke
list board